任务ID	任务类型	任务名	任务描述	任务目标	任务前置副本	发布者头像	副本编号	SP点	金币奖励	经验奖励	钻石奖励	奖励物品编号
ID	Type	Name	Desc	Target	PreposeID	Icon	Scene	SP	Gold	Exp	Gem	Items
1000	1	Unknown girl	Betiwar:My warriors，the villagers rescued a girl in a coma from the foot of the mountain，she seems to have been pursued by the dark forces that fled here.Now I need your strength to drive off the entrenched group not far from the Monster.I have people to open the channel on the way where you can directly go there to fight.Remember the battle for survival，there is nothing more important than  this realization.	Clearance copy: City entrance	0	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7000	105	1210	1050	0	1014|1|1214|1|1414|1
1001	1	Drive out the monster	Betiwar:They temporarily hide in a deeper place，but this does not completely repulse them.The girl is still in a coma，dark forces caused her stress so that she could not completely wake up.I felt the goddess signal will protect her safe and sound and eventually help her to wake up.	Clearance copy: Entrance into the black mist	7000	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7001	110	1220	1100	0	3014|1|3214|1|3414|1
1002	1	Necromancer's breath	Madeleine West:I have heard from Betiwar that you，your strength should not be overlooked.Betiwar is now treating the poor little girl，so do not worry too much.His therapy is very famous.Before fighting though，do you young people want to know how to practice your hand at battle?  In order to understand your weapon，you must also spend time in deep thought with it.	Clearance copy: The land of the dead	7001	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7002	115	1230	1150	0	10000|1
1003	1	Look for the source of the darkness underground.	Madeleine West:The place turned out to be a relic，at the time also caused quite a stir，so no one knows what is actually stored in the grounds of the castle.There are many Cabalists and people like you that went there to check it，but they are clueless.Go and clean this place up，I don't believe you will come to any harm.	Clearance copy: Alley	7002	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7003	120	1240	1200	0	10000|4
1004	1	Ancient city whispers	"Madeleine West:Goblins that originally belong in jungle，have suddenly become irritable and aggressive.Although you were away from the hustle and bustle of the glorious town，it has grown a lot,It is rare to see a strong young talent.Betiwar told me that he has a hunch that you will become the key to the war.Although I do not understand the meaning，he must have his reasons."	Clearance copy: Golin gathering	7003	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7004	125	1250	1250	0	10101|1
1005	1	Silly monster	Shadow:Madeleine West wants me to wait for you here.I am a shadow，belonging to Shadow Hunter.He asked me to tell you if your ability is strong enough，you can continue to challenge the underground city of monsters.Of course，pay attention to their own safety，after all，you like him are brave and decisive.Young people，I wish you good luck.I hope you can return to me safe and sound.	Clearance copy: Camps	7004	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7005	130	1260	1300	0	4013|1|4213|1|4413|1
1006	1	Sharp knife	"Shadow:I began to feel that you do have a certain strength and the courage to accept the next challenge.Remember，the more deep the depths you walk，Monsters will be more brutal and cold-blooded,You need to be more cautious in order to protect yourself."	Clearance copy: Ancient depths	7005	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7006	135	1270	1350	0	
1007	1	Penetrate the dark space of the wind	"Madeleine West:Shadow told me that she recognized you as a fighter that shows strength，which is something to celebrate.I've just been told by my subordinates East Kipling，a town resident has unknowingly strayed into the underground city when the entrance was opened,You must find him and protect his safety."	Clearance copy: The wind is whistling	7006	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7007	140	1280	1400	0	2013|1|2213|1|2413|1
1008	1	Goblin carnival	Madeleine West:No residents? It is along the road towards a deeper place where you must go，this is not a pleasant thing.It’s a very deep kind of place，and one can not guarantee you will survive.You must continue into the deep city，to find his whereabouts.	Clearance copy: Goblin's crafty smile	7007	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7008	145	1290	1450	0	
1009	1	In a flash，the blade is stained with blood	Madeleine West:The murderous monster will not mistake an ordinary human.At least try to find the person's possessions.Though hope is slim，do not give up.Hopefully the goddess will use her splendor to help the poor lost people back to safety.She will do the same for Betiwar and the girl in a come，so you shouldn't worry.	Clearance copy: Land of skeletons	7008	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7009	150	1300	1500	0	5013|1|5213|1|5413|1
1010	1	A town built on quicksand	"Betiwar:Glad to see you once again standing in front of me.Madeleine West and shadow invariably expressed to me their appreciation for you,In the time I treated the girl，you've been challenging the Dark Monster's strength.The girl has woken from her coma，and she seems to refer to a small town called Quicksand.Apparently there is a brutal monster there that needs to be dealt with，so I must entrust this work unto you."	Clearance copy: The town Quicksand	7009	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7010	155	1310	1550	0	
1011	1	The sand that stiffles cries	Betiwar:After the invasion of sand，the Monsters came and broke into the border of the town brining death.I vaguely can remember that many years ago I've been there ......young man，you must go to the town to see how much Monster has damaged.	Clearance copy: Dune	7010	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7011	160	1320	1600	0	1022|1|1222|1|1422|1
1012	1	Hissing danger signals	Shadow:The danger in the desert isnot only from the harsh weather.Carefully listen to the wind，and hidden in the sand dunes theres a hissing sound.It is a harbinger of imminent death.	Clearance copy: Current wind	7011	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7012	165	1330	1650	0	
1013	1	Fairy laughter	Shadow:There was a strange rumor in the small town that if one witnessed these kind of gems with the naked eye，it drove you mad.The minerals seem to eminate fairy laughter.A lot of people took it as kinds of fairy gifts，and flocked to search the depths of the dunes，but many people do not come back.From these rumors，it seems they they are not good goblins.So go check on those strange species.	Clearance copy: Barren land	7012	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7013	170	1340	1700	0	3022|1|3222|1|3422|1
1014	1	Snake skin	"Shadow:Is that right? Those with long and strange curly tail，they have a have camouflaged fangs that shoot poison.The are arrogant also from the ability to shed their old skin like a snake to reveal the new perfect skin underneath,Humans are not so stupid could to be confused by these creatures."	Clearance copy: Living tail	7013	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7014	175	1350	1750	0	
1015	1	Altered species	Madeleine West:I received the news from the film，mentioned in the letter of the town you encountered，Quicksand.Surprisingly，as shadow mentioned，she could smell dragons breath on your body，which is quite a dangerous species.Recorded from ancient times，dragon has always represented of bloodthirsty cruelty.I do not know what is actually there，so I must ask you to go check it out.	Clearance copy: The belly of the dragon	7014	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7015	180	1360	1800	0	4022|1|4222|1|4422|1
1016	1	Pterodatcyl rolling over the winds	"Madeleine West:Dragon wings，have been something that people fear to see.But they do not know the relationship between these and the snakeskin monster living among the sand.There are giant creatures flying behin the wind that is blocking people's vision,Perhaps this is one reason why they could become easily confused to be a fairy."	Clearance copy: Wing of a dragon	7015	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7016	185	1370	1850	0	
1017	1	Perilous	Madeleine West:It seems that the girl in a coma says the town has become a monster's paradise.The original people living there disappeared，perhaps they have become the dark force's food.We must clear the monsters out of this town.	Clearance copy: Prey	7016	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7017	190	1380	1900	0	2022|1|2222|1|2422|1
1018	1	Venom covered dragon tooth	Shadow:You should already know something about dragons，the dragon is very rare on this continent，and I must admit I have not seen before.I will be with you in the town to see this dark force of the dragon，and what actually caused the attack.	Clearance copy: Blood and venom	7017	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7018	195	1390	1950	0	
1019	1	Dragon blood	Betiwar:Shadow came back here before you，but because of the injury from your bit，the wound will not heal.I went through a lot of old books，only one mentioned that dragon's blood may be effective，so go and get me that，maybe only you can do it.	Clearance copy: Brutal desert	7018	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7019	200	1400	2000	0	5022|1|5222|1|5422|1
1020	1	Graveyard enveloped by darkness	"Betiwar:Shadow says Dragon Blood has been used for treatment on wounds，although not effective immediately.I thank you for your service.After that there is one thing I entrust to you，I received news of the girl，those who died in the battle，the remains of warriors are buried in the cemetery,Now they are being used by demons and destroyed.Would you please go to the cemetery and eradicate those demons."	Clearance copy: Cemetary	7019	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7020	205	1410	2050	0	
1021	1	Audible coffin	Betiwar:Buried in the cemetery，in addition to the death of innocent civilians，are those bright soldiers who sacrificed themselves.We do not have to be too sad for them in death，to believe they are not permanently dead.They will always stand here with us looking forward to the arrival of a more peaceful future for the continent.	Clearance copy: Moist soil	7020	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7021	210	1420	2100	0	1032|1|1232|1|1432|1
1022	1	In the moonlight	"Mysterious girl:In the bright moonlight，I stumbled through dark space，behind me was a continuous roar,I knew they were not far away and if I stopped I knew they would tear me to shreds.Suddenly，from underground outstretched a blue hand，that grabbed my feet.Its in the cemetery，the smell of death will suffocate me! Please save me!"	Clearance copy: Remembering the cemetary	7021	Icon20_Npc_Women_02	7022	215	1430	2150	0	
1023	1	Mournful zombie	Mysterious Girl:I feel their grief.The sleeping dead have been awakened making their soul's restless.Their rotting body exudes from the dark forces of the fog，I have to save them，but how do I do? Leading them back to the realm of the dead，is the real liberation.	Clearance copy: Harbringer of death	7022	Icon20_Npc_Women_02	7023	220	1440	2200	0	3032|1|3232|1|3432|1
1024	1	Sorcerer	Mysterious girl:Yes，I saw someone behind them holding a wand，spells wafting from his mouth.Under the effects of a spell，the ground zombies quickly get up after being knocked to the ground.He is a shaman of the dark forces coming wake the dead to turn them into his minions!	Clearance copy: Wizard residence	7023	Icon20_Npc_Women_02	7024	225	1450	2250	0	
1025	1	Soulless corpse	Betiwar:You've seen the girl， I felt closest to God in this light.I tried to ask her history，but she has some damage to the spirit，so she lost her memory.Her memories of what happened at the cemetery have made her tired，she needs to rest for a while.Follow her description to the cemetary and destroy those strange creatures.	Clearance copy: Gathering corpses	7024	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7025	230	1460	2300	0	4032|1|4232|1|4432|1
1026	1	Decaying organisms	Madeleine West:Rotting organisms can be particularly pleasureable to stab up，don't you think? Young warrior，tell me your weapons are excitedly looking forward to splitting the group of heretics biological bodies.	Clearance copy: Blood graves	7025	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7026	235	1470	2350	0	
1027	1	Monster chewing on corpses	Madeleine West:This cemetery was once the continent's most famous cemetery for burials，since many people believe in the goddesses.But the glory of the goddess is shielded from this land，so this place has become a battlefield shrouded by darkness.Thinking of it really makes this old man very angry.	Clearance copy: Cemetary at night	7026	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7027	240	1480	2400	0	2032|1|2232|1|2432|1
1028	1	The return of the dead	Betiwar:It will wake up those who are innocent，to become a puppet of the dark forces.I have already begun to chant a spell for you，the goddess's blessing.Your weapon will guide those people led astray，to return to their place.	Clearance copy: Reborn	7027	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7028	245	1490	2450	0	
1029	1	Falling into the dark sorceror	"Betty Will:Thoroughly clear cemetery，killing the walking dead or anyone choosing to associate with dark wizards.They made such a choice,and will surely pay for it.Cassandra，I take that girl's name.I will begin to enter her dreams，she came here to explore the purpose."	Clearance copy: The depths of the cemtery.	7028	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7029	250	1500	2500	0	5032|1|5232|1|5432|1
1030	1	The rive of life running through mother earth	"Madeleine West:Have you heard throughout the continent of the river Oka? She is named the edaravone.Even this remote town，also relies on the edaravone.But now the source of the river's strength is being sabataged by the dark forces.It is gradually drying up,So our battle will to the explore the threat to the river in the canyon.Repel all the monsters who occupy the river."	Clearance copy: The edge of the river	7029	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7030	255	1510	2550	0	
1031	1	Withered river bed	Madeleine West:the river is now a dry riverbed，the water has gradually been depleted.Those Monsters occupying the river will bring us a deadly threat.Go along the river and save our precious water.	Clearance copy: Downstream flood	7030	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7031	260	1520	2600	0	1042|1|1242|1|1442|1
1032	1	Sheeps head monster	Madeleine West:Sheepshead monster? You must mean the sheep orc clan.Orcs on this continent have a big family，the orc clan is wise and brave，and are very tough enemies.You must be more courageous than they in order to overcome them.May the goddess to give you courage.Conquer all!	Clearance copy: Sheep clan orc camp	7031	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7032	265	1530	2650	0	
1033	1	The flames of the dragon	"Shadow:What? I've heard there are dragons appearing and wonder how many strange creatures the dark forces have awakened.Our battles in the future are unknown,but we'll probably meet with a group of nasty creatures,We must punish them，they should not have come here from the darkness of the world to disrupt the world order."	Clearance copy: Blocked rivers	7032	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7033	270	1540	2700	0	3042|1|3242|1|3442|1
1034	1	The cry of Endaravone	Shadow:Madeleine West has told you the origins of this river.For centuries，people rely on the mainland Oka for her gift，a peaceful life.And now，I hear the mother's moaning sound came from the sky，the wind brings the cries of her spirit.Young warrior，we need more power to save her.	Clearance copy: The river's lament	7033	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7034	275	1550	2750	0	
1035	1	River's lament	Shadow:Along the direction of the river，put an end to the Monster's responsible for cutting off the flow of water.	Clearance copy: Down the river	7034	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7035	280	1560	2800	0	4042|1|4242|1|4442|1
1036	1	Oath of Shining Glory	Shadow:In the most upstream of the river edaravone，there is a book that is blessed by the goddess.Use it to protect yourself against the forces of darkness and the edaravone invasion.Now you have to go there，and make sure the book of vows is intact.Hopefully it has not been swallowed by darkness.	Clearance copy: Upstream	7035	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7036	285	1570	2850	0	
1037	1	Soldier's knife and sheild	"Shadow:Surrounded by a variety of dark creatures? According to the Book of Oaths，it is a rare energy source,Silly Monsters.By trying to infect the Book of Oaths it has destroyed them in their vain attempt."	Clearance copy: Book deposit	7036	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7037	290	1580	2900	0	2042|1|2242|1|2442|1
1038	1	Sinister master	Shadow:The soldiers have been taken over by evil forces，full of darkness and nothingness is their reality.Face them，and raise your weapon，it will be a  powerful deterrent to them.	Clearance copy: Polluted Rivers	7037	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7038	295	1590	2950	0	
1039	1	Frost dragon	Shadow:I swear，one day，I will personally kill those rebellious animals，including the legendary dragon! Before that，only you will be able to take of them.	Clearance copy: Frost dragon	7038	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7039	300	1600	3000	0	5042|1|5242|1|5442|1
1040	1	Fantasy water city	Betiwar:In addition to what you know，other than Endaravone mother river in the Oka continent，there are still other legendary waters.One is hidden in the depths of the forest，the legendary lake in the moonlight.Under the guidance of the moonlight through the fog on the lake you can reach the legendary City of Fantasy.Even though the records say it is beautiful，no one has come back alive from the forest.You must step into this unknown territory.	Clearance copy: Lake Island	7039	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7040	305	1610	3050	0	
1041	1	A variety of inferior species	Betiwar:Congratulations，you come back alive，this is the gift of the goddess.A piece of the legendary waters have been contaminated by the dark forces? Or，the waters already belonged to the dark dark forces ......	Clearance copy: Underwater city	7040	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7041	310	1620	3100	0	1052|1|1252|1|1452|1
1042	1	Sea warrior clan	Betty Will:Books do not document this mysterious City of Fantasy creatures，this is a very regrettable thing.I must admit my ignorance，which is self-honesty.Cassandra mentioned in a dark dream of hers that there is a mysterious organism that lives in this City of Fantasy.These mysterious creatures crawled out from the soil and seem to hide a secret.	Clearance copy: A cave	7041	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7042	315	1630	3150	0	
1043	1	Ice wall	Betiwar:I entered her dream，and in Cassandra's dream the water left on the wall，ice crystals.Underwater creatures were struggling and changing in the dark，becoming driven by the dark devil.	Clearance copy: Frozen walls	7042	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7043	320	1640	3200	0	3052|1|3252|1|3452|1
1044	1	Breaking the ice	Betiwar:Break the ice to gain access into the City of Fantasy.I believe that dreams Cassandra's dreams are real signs，she will become a key to our struggle with the dark forces.	Clearance copy: Inside the Fantasy City	7043	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7044	325	1650	3250	0	
1045	1	A burning flame in the dark	Betiwar:Those that use information from dark ritual methods you will help them meet their maker.Whether with flame or other forces，they can not really hurt you.Even if the glorious goddess was frozen underwater，it still will not subside.	Clearnace copy: The world of illusions	7044	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7045	330	1660	3300	0	4052|1|4252|1|4452|1
1046	1	Hidden in the dark eyes	Madeleine West:On your body is a smell I am so familiar with ......reminds me of a long time ago，the first time I met the man.It might have been in the fantasy city where you go this smell，so he might still be near here.Go back there so I can confirm that he is in that city.	Clearance copy: fantasy city crossroads	7045	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7046	335	1670	3350	0	
1047	1	Rays of crystal	"Madeleine West:It is indeed Landon's scent,I find it suprising that he was able to steal a stone as strong as this.His strength is comparible with Betiwar，who worships in the hall of the high priest，and even has greater rights than Betiwar，in the end is what attracted him to give up all this and stoop so low? You should continue an in-depth study of this man."	Clearance copy: The forces of evil	7046	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7047	340	1680	3400	0	2052|1|2252|1|2452|1
1048	1	Cassandra's abilities	Madeleine West:Betiwar told me about the mysterious girl he called Cassandra，that has the supreme ability to predict the future.Maybe a spokesman of God.I wonder whether this mysterious girl has such a capacity.But since she came here，where the speed of dark forces approach seems to be more accelerated.It seems the dark forces are coveting her power.	Clearance copy: Dark depths	7047	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7048	345	1690	3450	0	
1049	1	The blue secret ice stone begins to appear	Betty Will:I saw in her dream，a dream that wth blue light ......brilliant blue colors that were very familiar.They were radiating from a brilliant blue secret ice stone.Is it perhaps hidden in the City of Fantasy?  I have worked with Renton，the co-guardian of the blue secret ice stone for a very long time.In the depths of the City of Fantasy，it may also be hiding something.	Clearance copy: The deepest depths	7048	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7049	350	1700	3500	0	5052|1|5252|1|5452|1
1050	1	Boundaries of Ice and Fire	"Betiwarl:Through the ice it creates an illusion，a shattered mirror displaying nothingness.After hiding in the fires of hell，it burned everything,It was part of the flame of the world，buring all who tread on it，through firewall，you will be our only hope to save this continent."	Clearance copy: The boundaries of ice and fire	7049	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7050	355	1710	3550	0	
1051	1	Flowing lava	"Shadow:A long time ago，in order to practice，I went alone to the volcano，where hot air can train a person's will,This place took much patience and grit to bear the heat and puched one's will to the limit.As an extinct volcano，it is a suitable place for something strange to hide."	Clearance copy: Firewall	7050	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7051	360	1720	3600	0	1062|1|1262|1|1462|1
1052	1	Mysterious and sinister sorceror	Shadow:There is indeed an extinct volcano.Since the forces of darkness began to erode everything on the continent，magma beneath the volcano has been awakened.A surge of waves began to roll out，the slumbering volcano was now awake.Believe me，this is not good news good.Eliminate surrounding monsters，and this might reduce the burden on top of the volcano.	Clearance copy: Stopping the blaze	7051	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7052	365	1730	3650	0	
1053	1	The entrance to the volcano	"Shadow:I have tried to close the entrance of the volcano，but the weather is very bad,Plus the closer I get，the more crazy the monsters.So far，my left arm has been burned by the blue flames.I know you're a very brave man，but be careful，sometimes fear is good for us."	Clearance copy: Entrance to the volcano	7052	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7053	370	1740	3700	0	3062|1|3262|1|3462|1
1054	1	Deep magma	Shadow:You are indeed a rare warrior，young man.Continue through to the hot magma，although I do not know how excactly you will reach your destination but there is no other choice.	Clearance copy: Surging magma	7053	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7054	375	1750	3750	0	
1055	1	Magic ball	Shadow:A seat that rises magically from the groun? It seems its not that unusual here.I seem to hear the rush and roar of underground magma，and a voice that comes from the earth in lament.It seems time is running out，this situation must be reported to Betiear.Go destroy those bastards.	Clearance copy: Magma flowing through the land	7054	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7055	380	1760	3800	0	4062|1|4262|1|4462|1
1056	1	Laughter of ghosts from underground	Betiwar:Ah my warriors，when you go into the hot crater，looking for a glimmer of hope to save the world，I did not stop entering Cassandra's dreams and following her footsteps.In her dreams，from hot underground came sinister laughter.The laughter was from a demon.Go underground to go check it out，and her dreams will guide you to get there.	Clearance copy: Burning underground	7055	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7056	385	1770	3850	0	
1057	1	Pursuing the rays of light	"Betiwar:Remember what I mentioned about the blue ice secret stone? In the records，the goddess returned leaving this blue ice secret stone.This sealed the continent of all the dark creatures and evil forces.But Landon the stole secret stone，destroying the seal  and now everything has undergone enormous changes.As long as there is a clue I will not give up.I will not stop seeking the secret stone,Let it shine through the world and restore peace."	Clearance copy: Undergroudn cage	7056	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7057	390	1780	3900	0	2062|1|2262|1|2462|1
1058	1	Hunter's blade	Shadow:I polished your weapons，now go test the results.Monsters blood will make it even more sharp.	Clearnce copy: Evil gathering place	7057	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7058	395	1790	3950	0	
1059	1	Hope is shining through the flames	Betiwar:Please forgive my manners，I wasn't wrong about what I saw in Cassandra's dream.It is indeed the blue ice secret stone that he stole away from its fortified place.Inside the black box hides her glory.I felt the heat around，so therefore it must be linked to the monsters in the volcano.	Clearance copy: Volcanic underground layer	7058	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7059	400	1800	4000	0	5062|1|5262|1|5462|1
1060	1	Depths of the forest temple	Betiwar:I woke up to see that I was surrounded by a delapidated temple and surrounded by dense forest.Because of the war，many of the continent's temples dedicated to the goddess have been damaged.But to find the tall temple is not difficult to do.I have found there a door that you can take that leads to the temple.	Clearance copy: Deep in the forest	7059	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7060	405	1810	4050	0	
1061	1	Destruction of statues	Betiwar:The reason why they constructed the temple deep in the forest was because the legend that it was once a place where miracles happened.So to commemorate the establishment of God's footprints they built it.A long time ago it was very well frequented as there were many believers，but when people's faith started to fade，they deserted this place.This is God's sorrow，but also human tragedy.Drive off those monsters，they should not interfere with God's peace.	Clearance copy: Inaccessible places	7060	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7061	410	1820	4100	0	
1062	1	Snarl of the Ox-headed man	Madeleine West:The temple has been occupied by Orcs.The ox-headed people forgot the temple in the ignorance and forgot what brought hope to this continent.	Clearance copy: Temple entrance	7061	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7062	415	1830	4150	0	
1063	1	Abandoned faith	Madeleine West:The power of faith who support us out of the mountains，to build the wall，so that people come together to become stronger，against all the evil forces.Young man tell me，do you still believe in the power of God? Or like those people who have been eroded by the darkness，have you abandonded the faith and let greed occupy your heart?	Clearance copy: Hover on the edge	7062	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7063	420	1840	4200	0	
1064	1	Pages stained with blood	"Shadow:That temple is said to be the place where the Goddess showed herself，so old people will go to worship there.As for its reasons for the decline，people gradually forgot the existence of the goddess.The tall temple has gradually become desolate.It is documented that a holy book is hidden in the temple,Go look for it carefully but don't be surprised if you can't find it."	Clearance copy: Inside the Temple	7063	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7064	425	1850	4250	0	
1065	1	Soldier holding a large hammer	"Shadow:A soldier holding a large hammer? It is probably Thor，a mysterious race，living in the ground，with unparalleled strength and strong body,I've only encountered them before when I used to practice religion and took a trip underground.They are a tough race to deal with so be careful of their attacks."	Clearance copy: A living hammer	7064	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7065	430	1860	4300	0	
1066	1	A dancer in dreamland	Betiwar:In Cassandra's dreams，in the deep there was a tall temple and a girl dancing.I have tried to sneak into the depths of her dreams to look for the girl，but you can only see the distant figure.But the girl is so similar to Cassandra，I wonder is she is the same person?	Clearance copy: Pyschic dreams	7065	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7066	435	1870	4350	0	
1067	1	Goddess's tears	"Betiwar:I dream of gods sheding tears ......Its probably because of allthe times I've recently visited other people's dreams.I believe this is the goddess trying to guide us,The tall temple is so desolate and has made the gods lonely.Go to the place where the statue is and expell all of the surrounding monsters."	Clearance copy: Place of the fallen temple	7066	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7067	440	1880	4400	0	
1068	1	The power of faith	Madeleine West:Faith is a very strange power when you believe in her presence，she can really make you fearless.When you abandon her，she immediately becomes worthless.That said，I don't mean it to be discouraging but to remind you that your faith is a resource of power.	Clearance copy: Temple depths	7067	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7068	445	1890	4450	0	
1069	1	Purification ceremony	Betiwar:Those dark creatures like bugs are disgusting.I suddenly had an ominous premonition that the strange dancing girl is sent as a guide from the goddess.If so，then thank God，she did not give up on us.	Clearance copy: The place where the girl dances.	7068	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7069	450	1900	4500	0	
1070	1	Shrine	"Shadow:The dark forces attacks are ever increasing,You probably do not know，but the town's shrine to worship the goddess is in the center,Behind a barrier，that is.This barrier protecting the town，so the dark forces still maintain a lull.But this barrier is constantly dissipating.Betiwar has traveled to check it out，so you must go with him and protect his safety."	Clearance copy: Shrine gate	7069	Icon20_Npc_Women_01	7070	455	1910	4550	0	
1071	1	Blood stained fresco	Betiwar:How did you get here? Did the shado bring you? While we were busy unraveling the mystery of the dancing girl the protective barrier is crumbling away.I must find out why，once the barrier disappears，the town will be under attack.Madeleine and Kipling have traveled deep towards the shrine.I will travel on the outside and try to fix the weak barrier.You must go to the depths，to help them.	Clearance copy: Protected areas	7070	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7071	460	1920	4600	0	
1072	1	The centaur	Betiwar:You can't find them? They are probably already very deep within.I felt a strange creatures breath from within the shrine，but how do you think they got in there? You go to destroy them，and look out for clues.	Clearance copy: The centaurs appear	7071	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7072	465	1930	4650	0	
1073	1	The evil worship of the Thor people	Betiwar:Is that right? The Thor people were the cause of this? Thor family is a very mysterious race，they are recorded as living in places where humans can't enter.The forces of darkness has probably turned them crazy now.I'm not worried that you would be obstructed by them.And besides，worrying will cause another situation that I won't be able to understand.	Clearance copy: The Thor people appear again	7072	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7073	470	1940	4700	0	
1074	1	Soldoers charging forward	East Kipling:I am a barbarian warrior and Madeleine West's faithful guardian.As long as I live，will not allow any strange creatures to harm Madeleine! Even though my knee now has an arrow in it and can not I can't drag my hind legs.But the Elders made me stay here.I knew Betiwar would send someone to catch up.Madeleine West had to move on，but it seems many strange things are surrounding us ......	Clearance copy: Soldier with arrow in the knee	7073	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	7074	475	1950	4750	0	
1075	1	Depths of the shrine	"Madeleine West:You actually got here! It seems that Betiwar needs to understand the seriousness of the situation.Renton and the secret stone are constantly calling us closer，but I do not know whether this is a trap.You must help me destroy monsters here，then go back to Betiwar,And remember that I will come back with the secret stone! Do not continue deeper!"	Clearance copy: Passageway of the shrine	7074	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7075	480	1960	4800	0	
1076	1	The odor disappears	"Betiwar:Madeleine West told you? I really sense the call of the gems from the depths，but I understand that they are very likely to be a full set! Madeleine takes too many risks.I feel that the light of the gems are disappearing，this is a dangerous omen,Cassandra is sleeping again,so I will sneak into her dream to see if there are more clues.I need you to continue into the depths of the shrine and follow Madeleine's trail."	Clearance copy: Surrounded by the monsters	7075	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7076	485	1970	4850	0	
1077	1	Furious warrior	Kipling:Those bastards of the darkness! How dare they try to stop me from following Madeleine's footsteps，all of these monsters must die! But there are too many of these bastards ......please help me.	Clearance copy: Blocked	7076	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	7077	490	1980	4900	0	
1078	1	Splinter of precious gem	Madeleine West:Are we too late? I clearly saw the magic stone in front of us，but when I reached out to touch it，it suddenly cracked and disappeared.Then leaving only debris when it fell to the ground.I'm not sure whether Betiwar knows what is going on here，you must keep on killing monsters.Go to Betiwar and I will stay here continue and continue to investigate.	Clearance copy: The place for the blue secret stone	7077	Icon20_Npc_Man_02	7078	495	1990	4950	0	
1079	1	The sleeping girl	Betiwar:The secret stone has once again disappeared.Another piece of news，then I will tell you reason for her dissapearance.Cassandra's dream enters into the darkness，if her secret dream about fate of the secret stone，at least she is safe.Go once again into the shrine to clean it out，the danger of the protective barriers disappearing is gone.About secret stone，I must once again think about how to locate her.	Clearance copy: The girl in deep sleep	7078	Icon20_Npc_Man_01	7079	500	2000	5000	0	
2000	2	BountyDevil Cave (1)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (1)	7009	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8001	300	2500	4500	0	6112|1
2001	2	Bountyspace-time (1)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (1)	7009	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8002	300	2500	4500	0	6712|1
2002	2	BountyDevil Cave (2)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (2)	7019	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8011	400	3000	5000	0	6122|1
2003	2	Bountyspace-time (2)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (2)	7019	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8012	400	3000	5000	0	6722|1
2004	2	BountyDevil Cave (3)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (3)	7029	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8021	500	3500	5500	0	6132|1
2005	2	Bountyspace-time (3)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (3)	7029	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8022	500	3500	5500	0	6732|1
2006	2	BountyDevil Cave (4)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (4)	7039	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8031	600	4000	6000	0	6142|1
2007	2	Bountyspace-time (4)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (4)	7039	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8032	600	4000	6000	0	6742|1
2008	2	BountyDevil Cave (5)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (5)	7049	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8041	700	4500	6500	0	6152|1
2009	2	Bountyspace-time (5)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (5)	7049	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8042	700	4500	6500	0	6752|1
2010	2	BountyDevil Cave (6)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (6)	7059	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8051	800	5000	7000	0	6162|1
2011	2	Bountyspace-time (6)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (6)	7059	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8052	800	5000	7000	0	6762|1
2012	2	BountyDevil Cave (7)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (7)	7069	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8061	900	5500	7500	0	6172|1
2013	2	Bountyspace-time (7)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (7)	7069	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8062	900	5500	7500	0	6772|1
2014	2	BountyDevil Cave (8)	"East Kipling :the people to battle,while occasionally encounter cases lost,accidentally opened the cave filled with evil.The depths of the cave came the roar of the beast,fishy odor nostrils, and in the deepest faintly visible brilliant gems.Rumors as long as you are brave enough,through the cave,and you will be able to get the strength to match the incentives go, the Warriors,it was a great adventure!"	Clearance copy: Demon Cave (8)	7079	Icon20_Npc_Man_03	8071	1000	6000	8000	0	6182|1
2015	2	Bountyspace-time (8)	"Alpha :Due to the various regions to combat the door completely on the power of the members of the worship hall opened and maintained.The majority of church members worship after a long battle,a serious shortage of power.In the process of maintaining the door open a short time and space will appear to jump,resulting in a space-time.Accidentally strayed into the cracks,apart from fighting to the last moment,you have no choice.But believe me, dear warrior,you'll get belong and pay the corresponding reward.Break those cracks in our fight will be of great help."	Clearance copy: space-time (8)	7079	Icon20_Npc_Man_04	8072	1000	6000	8000	0	6782|1
